<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Minecraft: Turtle Server</title><link>https://info.mcturtles.org/</link><description>Recent content on Minecraft: Turtle Server</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://info.mcturtles.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://info.mcturtles.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.mcturtles.org/about/</guid><description>Minecraft: Turtle Server is a whitelist enabled survival server. A creative world is also available for working on collaborative design projects.
The Beginning In the fall of 2019, a fellow turtle decided to create a singleplayer world. They played with a couple of their friends on LAN and began to build and develop the world.
After that day, the decision was made to put this on a permanent server. After this, slowly, more and more players were added and a fledgling world came to be.</description></item><item><title>Governance</title><link>https://info.mcturtles.org/governance/governance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.mcturtles.org/governance/governance/</guid><description>Minecraft: Turtle Server needs to be hosted by someone. This document outlines how that the administration of the server and governance over changes will be done.
The current server admin is Gary Kim.
Overview Governance is done in a fashion similar to the liberal contribution model used in open source software development. The general philosophy that we are using is that all opinions are worth considering. The server admin must not make changes to server configuration without a general consensus after an appropriate attempt to contact everyone who may be effected by a change.</description></item><item><title>Locations</title><link>https://info.mcturtles.org/locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.mcturtles.org/locations/</guid><description>Within Minecraft Turtle Server&amp;rsquo;s world there are dozens of landmarks, and a multitude of key areas. Listed below are some places of note
Spawn Forest Town Homestead Sorry Island Alterac Founder&amp;rsquo;s Abode Lud The Mountain Base The Shopping District Founder&amp;rsquo;s Abode The Pit Tundra Stables Industrial Flower Island</description></item><item><title>Whitelist</title><link>https://info.mcturtles.org/governance/whitelist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.mcturtles.org/governance/whitelist/</guid><description>This document outlines the process for adding or removing players from the whitelist.
Also refer to the governance overview.
The addition or removal of players from the whitelist will follow the same process as changes to server configuration. Any player may propose the addition of a player to the group. As long as there is no objection to the addition of the player by any current player, they will be added to the whitelist.</description></item></channel></rss>